// Setting up questions array 

var questions = 
[
  {
    question: "Who is the Current Captain of the Blackhawks?",
    a:"Jonathan Toews", 
    b:"Duncan Keith",
    c:"Brent Seabrook",
    answer: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "What Year did the Blackhawks win the Cup last?",
    a:"2015",
    b:"2016",
    c:"2014",
    answer: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "What Year Did the BlackHawks first win the Cup?",
    a:"1960", 
    b:"1984",
    c:"1934",
    answer: "C"

  },
  {
    question: "Who Won the Conn Smythe Trophy (Playoff MVP Award) in 2013?",
    a:"Jonathan Toews", 
    b:"Patrick Kane", 
    c:"Duncan Keith",
    answer: "B"
  },
  {
    question: "Who Became the 'hero' of the Chicago Blackhawks in 2010 when Christobal Huet got injured?",
    a:"Dustin Byfuglien",
    b:"Kris Versteeg",
    c:"Annti Niemi",
    answer: "C"
  },
  {
    question: "Who did the Blackhawks face in the Western Conference Finals in 2014? Hint: Game 7 Heartbreaker",
    a:"Los Angeles Kings",
    b:"San Jose Sharks",
    c:"Anaheim Ducks",
    answer: "A"
  },
 
  {
    question: "HARD: Who scored the Triple Overtime Goal in Game 2 of the Western Conference Finals 2015?",
    a:"Brent Seabrook",
    b:"Andrew Shaw",
    c:"Marcus Kruger",
    answer: "C"
  },
  {
    question: "HARD: Who was the Hero in Game 5 of the 2015 Stanley Cup Finals, scoring the Go-ahead Goal in the 3rd Period?",
    a: "Duncan Keith",
    b:"Antoinne Vermette",
    c:"Patrick Kane",
    answer: "B"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the Most Recent Blackhawk to win the Hart Memorial Trophy (Regular Season MVP)?",
    a:"Jonathan Toews",
    b:"Artemi Panarin",
    c:"Patrick Kane",
    answer: "C"
  },
  {
    question: "Who are the Chicago Blackhawks AHL Affiliate?",
    a:"Chicago Wolves",
    b:"Rockford IceHogs", 
    c:"Iowa Wild",
    answer: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "When was Patrick Kane Drafted into the NHL?",
    a:"2005",
    b:"2009", 
    c:"2007",
    answer: "B"
  },
  {
    question: "HARD: When was the last time the Blackhawks faced an Original Six Opponent in the Finals?",
    a:"2013",
    b:"2010",
    c:"2014",
    answer: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "HARD: Whos goal was disallowed in 2013 in a Game 7 with less than a minute to play?",
    a:"Niklas Hjalmarsson",
    b:"Brent Seabrook",
    c:"Johnny Oduya",
    answer: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "Who was recently drafted 3rd Overall by the Blackhawks in 2019?",
    a:"Alex Nylander",
    b:"Kirby Dach",
    c:"Adam Boqvist",
    answer: "B"
  },
  {
    question: "Who was known as the 'Russian Kane' in his Scouting Report?",
    a:"Artemi Panarin",
    b:"Ilya Kovalchuk",
    c:"Alex Ovechkin",
    answer: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "HARD BONUS: Who scored the First Goal for the BlackHawks in the 2013 Stanley Cup Final?",
    a:"Brandon Saad",
    b:"Andrew Shaw",
    c:"Dave Bolland",
    answer: "A"
  },
  {
    question: "HARD: Patrick Sharp is quoted saying a key player got injured in Game 6 of the 2010 Stanley Cup Finals, likely not going to play in Game 7 if necessary had Patrick Kane had not scored. Who was it?",
    a:"Dustin Byfuglien",
    b:"Duncan Keith",
    c:"Jonathan Toews",
    answer: "C"
  },
];
